beaconhouse.edu.pk 2010-12-09

# Privacy Statement

The Beaconhouse School System website is an information system intended to present an integrated view of the Beaconhouse School System to the members of the System community, as well as to alumni, prospective students and others with an interest in Beaconhouse.

  Site Traffic Statistics  
If you visit this site to view or download information, a standard log file will record:

This data is used in the aggregate for purposes of analysing site traffic and providing accountability regarding the usefulness of our work. Such analysis is not made at the level of the individual user.

  Personal Data  
Personal information about you is not gathered when you visit the Beaconhouse School System website unless you choose to supply that information to us (for example, by filling out a form requesting information for a specific purpose).

  Disclosure to Third Parties  
Personal information collected on this website is not disclosed to third parties unless the third party is an institutionally authorised provider of services to the System. Users of these services are subject to the privacy policies established by the third party provider.

Links to Other Sites  
The School System website has links to external websites which are beyond its control. Beaconhouse School System is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these other websites, and suggests that you read their privacy statements, if they are available.

Questions or Comments  
Please contact us at info@beaconhouse.edu.pk with your queries or comments.
